export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which animal makes the sound 'Woof'?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Horse",
      option4: "Sheep",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the sound of a donkey commonly known as?",
      option1: "Bray",
      option2: "Neigh",
      option3: "Whinny",
      option4: "Bleat",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal's sound is described as 'Neigh'?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Horse",
      option4: "Sheep",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The sound 'Baa' is typically associated with which animal?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Horse",
      option4: "Sheep",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What sound does a monkey usually make?",
      option1: "Bark",
      option2: "Howl",
      option3: "Chirp",
      option4: "Screech",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal's sound is described as 'Quack'?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Monkey",
      option4: "Duck",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the sound of a dog called?",
      option1: "Bark",
      option2: "Bray",
      option3: "Neigh",
      option4: "Bleat",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal's sound is commonly known as 'Moo'?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Horse",
      option4: "Cow",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What sound does a horse typically make?",
      option1: "Quack",
      option2: "Neigh",
      option3: "Baa",
      option4: "Chirp",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The sound 'Bleat' is typically associated with which animal?",
      option1: "Dog",
      option2: "Donkey",
      option3: "Horse",
      option4: "Sheep",
      ans: 4,
    },
  ];
  